stylifyyourblog.com 2015-06-09

# Privacy Policy | Stylify Your Blog

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at **support@stylifyyourblog.com**.   
  
At _www.stylifyyourblog.com_ , the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by _www.stylifyyourblog.com_ and how it is used.   
  
**Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, _www.stylifyyourblog.com_ makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.   

******Advertising Partners**  
Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include .... **  
**  
Google AdSense  
**  
**  
These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on _www.stylifyyourblog.com_ send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.   
  
_www.stylifyyourblog.com_ has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.   
  
You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. _www.stylifyyourblog.com_ 's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.   
  
If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.   

**What we collect  **  
We may collect the following information:   

  * Name;
  * Contact information including email address;
  * Other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers. 

**  
**  
**What we do with the information we gather**    
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons: 

  * Internal record keeping. 
  * We may use the information to improve our products and services. 
  * We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided. 
  * From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customize the website according to your interests. 

**Security  **  
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.   

**How we use cookies  **  
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.   

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.   

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.   

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.   

**Links to other websites  **  
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
